As you were doing this research, did you draw any connections to what would be the reason why Black people would be sequestered into these spaces and not given the opportunity to have the same as the other groups?
I mean, for me, the simple answer is like white supremacy. And I hate that it's to me, it's that simple.
But I think that people forget that like America was quite literally founded on the human trafficking of Black people.
And then as soon as that human trafficking ended, we developed an apartheid system to segregate and kind of denounce the humanity of Black people once again.
All of the addendums we see, the amendments we see are focused on controlling, using, extracting resources and capital from Black people.
You recognizing your own humanity is one of the most powerful political acts and you have to be committed to it at all times because they're either going to be entertained by watching you die or by watching you do something superhuman.
And you got to decide if that's how you want to go about the rest of your life. But I can't do that. Personally, I can't.
I just feel like a proud auntie.
Oh, I can tell. Thank you.
They don't know. Like we go back from, I think I first met you when I was like six or five years old at a grassroots give thanks event in Newark.
Yeah. Like, yeah, it was all the way back.
I was doing some appearance, you know, for the kids and coming to hang out with the kids.
And, you know, but, you know, I don't know if you know this, but I believe the children are future.
Teach them well and let them be the way.